Eh?
什么？
Arai just went downstairs, right?
荒井刚才是走下楼了 没错吧？
Kobeni, make a double "peace" sign and stay where you are.
小红 你双手比“耶” 站在原地
Oh my…
我的天
Aki, what's going on?
阿秋 这是怎么回事？
It might be a Devil.
八成是恶魔的能力
Another room on the other side of the window?
为什么窗户的另一边也是房间？
Hey, we can't get out through the windows.
喂 不管从哪扇窗走都出不去
They all lead to the room directly across.
全都通往正对面的房间
Guessed so.
果然不出所料
We're stuck on the 8th floor.
我们被困在八楼了
There's no way out.
出不去了
Let's go through the situation.
来确认一下情况吧
It's most likely a Devil's trick.
恐怕是恶魔在搞鬼
We go back to the 8th floor whether we go up or downstairs.
不管从八楼楼梯往上或往下走
The elevator is somehow out of order.
电梯不知为什么用不了了
The rooms and windows don't lead outside.
无法从房间或窗户出去
We also go back to the 8th floor through the ceiling.
掀开天花板往上 一样会回到八楼
Is it because of the Devil Power killed?
是不是因为帕瓦杀死了那个恶魔？
It might've sealed us here before it died.
它还没解除困住人的能力 就死了
That Devil--
是那个恶魔…
-You told me to kill the Devil! -I did not!
-是你叫老子动手杀死恶魔的 -我没叫！
It's not possible. A Devil's power would die with it.
不可能 因为恶魔死后 能力会随之解除
Aki, the pieces have no reaction.
阿秋 肉片有没有产生反应？
Speaking of that,
关于这点
it just used that Devil as bait earlier.
反应完全消失了
And now it's keeping a low profile.
利用刚才的恶魔当诱饵 摆了我们一道
I've never seen such a wily Devil.
第一次遇到如此诡计多端的恶魔
But if we don't get back to headquarters in time,
但是假如我们迟迟没有出去
other Devil Hunters will come here to find us, right?
其他恶魔猎人应该会来救援吧
Let's hope they won't step into this trap as we did.
只能祈祷 他们不会像我们一样掉进陷阱
Every one of us will die here.
我们所有人都会死在这里
We'll starve to death…
一定会活活饿死…
K-Kobeni, be brave.
小红 振作
You're doing this job for your brother to go to university, aren't you?
你不是为了让哥哥上大学 才来当恶魔猎人的吗？
Half the reason is I'm forced to do this.
有一半是因为被逼的
My parents want to send only my smart brother to university.
我爸妈只想送优秀的哥哥上大学
And I'm told to make money.
叫我出来工作赚钱
It's either the sex industry or the Devil Hunter.
只能下海做特殊行业 不然就是当恶魔猎人
I want to go to university too.
其实我也想去读大学
But…
但是…
I'll die here.
我一定会死在这里
Your face…
你的表情…
You bitch!
臭家伙
Stop laughing.
别再笑了
Kobeni, fear is a Devil's favorite dish.
小红 恶魔最喜欢恐惧了
They want you to be scared.
你这么害怕 只是正中敌人的下怀
But I am scared.
但我就是会怕啊
Aki, you're acting strange too.
怎么连阿秋都不太对劲了？
The clock in the room…
房间里的时钟…
stays at 8:18.
从刚才开始一直停在8点18分
All the clocks on this floor are staying at 8:18.
不管是哪个房间的时钟
It might be a Devil
可能是由于恶魔的能力
So, no one will probably come for us.
这么一来 说不定没人能来营救
Great. Then I can sleep as long as I want.
好耶 这样我就能睡到爽为止
Are you an idiot?
你是白痴吗？
Maybe, maybe not.
有可能会 也有可能不会
Wake me up when you figure it out.
等你们弄清楚了再叫醒我吧
I'll gladly sleep and thank the Devil for this.
我会带着感激恶魔的心睡觉…
He really meant it…
还真的睡了…
Denji…
淀治
Time to get up.
差不多该起来了
You found a way out?
有办法离开八楼了吗？
Unfortunately, not yet.
很可惜 看样子目前还不行
While you were sleeping,
在你睡觉期间
we found out that the water supply and electricity are still working.
我们发现水电都还能使用
There's some food left by the guests who ran away.
还在房客逃走时所留下的行李中 找到一些食物
Frankly, everyone is almost at their limits.
坦白说 大家都快要到极限了
Aki keeps looking for the Devil.
阿秋不断寻找恶魔
He refused to take a rest.
我叫他休息一下 他都不听劝
Arai was supposed to go with Aki,
荒井本来帮阿秋一起找
but he locked himself in a room because he's too afraid of the situation.
现在却因为害怕这个状况
Kobeni went totally mad.
小红也疯掉了
She even wanted to drink from the toilet, so I knocked her out.
甚至想喝马桶的水 我就把她打晕了
As for the Fiend…
至于那位魔人…
What about Power?
帕瓦她怎么了吗？
I have nothing to do except think about the Nobel Prize.
老子闲得要命 一直在想诺贝尔奖的事
As long as my invention wins the Nobel Prize,
只要老子的发明赢得诺贝尔奖
humans will treat me like a god.
人类就会臣服于老子吧
Then I'll use the prestige to become the Prime Minister.
然后老子要拿诺贝尔奖当垫脚石
I want to see humans struggling…
因为老子想看人类饱受煎熬的惨样
The first thing I'll do is adjust the consumption tax to 100%.
第一步就是把消费税涨到100%
-She's always like that. -I see.
她平常就是这样
Good.
那就好
Let's keep a watch on Kobeni and Arai together.
我们三个一起监视小红跟荒井
I can't even go to the bathroom if I watch them alone.
只靠我的话 连厕所都去不了
Last cigarette.
这是最后一根烟了
It's so boring that you're so calm.
你未免太冷静了 真无聊
Aki is looking for the Devil. I can take a break.
阿秋正在努力寻找 所以我可以好好休息
With the power of nicotine.
再加上尼古丁的力量
It's a good thing to have something to rely on.
有东西能依赖是好事
It's my wish to live by relying on something else.
我的人生就是想倚靠别的东西过活
You smoke the same brand as Aki.
你跟他抽同一个牌子的烟耶
Because the person who taught him to smoke…
因为带阿秋领略烟的滋味的人
was me.
就是我
You don't smoke, Aki?
阿秋你不抽烟吗？
You should learn it to get around people.
为了跟人交际 还是学一下怎么抽烟吧
I don't plan to make friends.
我不打算跟任何人交好
Let me guess why you joined the Public Sector.
我来猜猜你为什么来当公安
You probably want to kill the Gun Devil, right?
八成是为了杀死枪之恶魔吧
It's always the case with those who came here with a poker face.
一脸阴沉来当公安的人都是这样
Because only we can keep Gun's pieces.
因为只有公安能持有枪混蛋的肉片
Devil Hunters are meant to die young, so what's the big deal about a cigarette?
恶魔猎人注定活不久 抽几根烟又何妨？
I won't die so easily.
我不会那么容易就死掉
Better keep your word.
你要说到做到喔
It always brings so much trouble when a teammate dies.
因为搭档死掉会很麻烦
Why did she…
刚才是怎么回事？
She's the girlfriend of a former teammate.
那是前搭档的女友
It happens very often to get ugly with a late teammate's family.
跟殉职搭档的眷属陷入纠纷 是常有的事
They can't take revenge on the Devil for their partner,
他们无力找恶魔报复
so they take it all out on me.
只好发泄在我身上
Yeah, I see it as part of the job being a Devil Hunter.
反正我就把忍受这种事 视为恶魔猎人工作的一部分
What did you do?
你跑去做什么了？
I stuck some gum on the clothes of the person who hit you.
我在那个打人的混蛋的衣服上
You should fight back if people hurt you.
被人伤害就该反击回去
You didn't do anything wrong.
问题不在你身上
I did that to her because I was pissed about this.
我就是觉得不爽
She deserves it.
这是她活该
She'll never realize that there's gum on her clothes.
那家伙这辈子都察觉不到 衣服上的口香糖
By the way, Master used to say
话说回来 师父以前说过
the Devil Hunter that those Devils fear the most
恶魔害怕的恶魔猎人
is neither the strong one nor the brave one,
既非强大的人 亦非勇敢的人
but the one who's a nutcase.
而是脑子不正常的家伙
So I think you can live a long life.
所以你一定能长命百岁
Are you making fun of me?
你是在挖苦我吗？
Give me the almond tofu if you don't want it.
不吃杏仁豆腐的话就给我吧
This one's for you.
给你一根
Cigarettes are bad for the bones. I don't want it.
吸烟伤骨头 我不要
I have a feeling that we'll be teammates for a long time.
我有预感我们能相处很久
I really hope you can smoke.
好希望你能抽烟
Just this one then.
我只陪你抽一根
I'll smoke just this once in my life.
我这辈子只会抽这一根烟
Himeno, do you have cigarettes?
姬野前辈 你身上还有烟吗？
Sadly, this is the last one.
很遗憾 这是最后一根
Fine.
真拿你没辙
It's a kiss! No fair! It's an indirect kiss!
是接吻 太贼了吧 这是间接接吻
Shut up.
闭嘴
Bad news.
有一个坏消息
The Devil we just killed.
我们不是杀了一个恶魔吗？
I killed it!
是老子杀掉的
That thing…
那个家伙…
is getting bigger and bigger.
变得越来越大了
But I did kill it…
老子明明确实杀掉它了…
A hotel we can't get out of.
出不去这间旅馆
A form I've never seen.
从没见过的形状…
What kind of Devil is this?
这到底是什么恶魔？
You humans.
你们这群人类
Stupid humans.
愚蠢的人类
I want to have a contract with you.
我要提出契约交涉
It's talking.
说话了
What contract?
什么契约？
Let me eat that human named Denji.
让我吃了那边那个叫淀治的人类
Alive or dead… Just let me eat him…
尸体也可以…让我吃了他…
Then I'll let everyone else leave here without a scratch.
我就让其他恶魔猎人 毫发无伤离开这里
I'll let you go back safe…
平安回去…
Sign the contract…
立下契约吧…
Denji…
淀治
Let it eat you.
让它吃了你吧
Aki, how about calling the fox to eat this thing?
阿秋 你召唤狐狸 吞掉这些就行了吧？
Kon.
叩
I guessed so.
狐狸果然没来
This place is completely isolated from the outside world.
这里与外界完全隔绝了
The fox's body is in Kyoto after all.
毕竟狐狸的本体在京都嘛
Let's use my ghost then.
那就用我的幽灵来解决吧
It hurts!
好痛
It's getting bigger!
变大了
This is not my real body.
这并非我的本体
My heart is not here.
我的心脏不在这里
This is just my stomach.
这里是胃的内部
You can't find me on the 8th floor.
我的弱点不在八楼
Sign the contract if you want to go home alive.
想活着回去 只能跟我立下契约
It probably won't let you go even if you let it eat me.
就算杀了我 它也不会放你们出去吧
Wrong.
不对喔
The Devil said it's a "contract."
那个恶魔不是说了 这是“契约”
The power of that word is immense when a Devil says it.
恶魔使用的“契约”这个词 蕴含强大的力量
As long as one party is abiding by the contract,
只要其中一方遵守契约
the other has to do the same.
另一方也绝对要遵守
Whoever breaches the contract will die.
违约的那一方必死无疑
We really can get out if we kill you.
所以只要杀死你 就真的能出去
Ms. Himeno, we should kill him.
姬野前辈 我们该杀了那家伙
We should kill him and go outside for any further discussion.
先杀死他 到外头拟定对策就行了
We'll all starve to death if we don't do anything.
维持现状 大家都会在宾馆里饿死
We should accept the offer!
我们应当接受那个恶魔的契约
The Devil wants Denji dead.
恶魔想杀死淀治
It means Denji's death is only beneficial for it.
就表示淀治的死亡对恶魔有利吧
So I refuse to sign.
所以我不接受契约
I refuse too then.
那我也不接受
What?
怎么这样…
I agree to kill him.
老子赞成杀死他
Even if I have an invention that can win the Nobel Prize,
就算想到能拿诺贝尔奖的发明
there's no way to publish it if I can't get out.
出不去的话也无法对外发表
So, die for my Nobel Prize.
你就为了诺贝尔奖去死吧
A Fiend can't sign a contract with a Devil.
魔人无法跟恶魔订立契约
So even if you killed Denji,
即便你杀死了淀治
the Devil wouldn't be obligated to let you out.
恶魔也没有义务放你出去
In short, we can't kill Denji.
总之不能杀了淀治
We are Devil Hunters.
我们身为恶魔猎人
We kill only Devils.
要杀的只有恶魔
It's so boring. Let's play Sumo!
无聊死了 我们来玩手推相扑吧
No! You always want to kill me!
不要 你是想马上杀掉我
I'm so hungry.
肚子好饿
Aki, tell me the truth. Did you think of a way to get out?
阿秋 老实说 你有没有逃脱的办法？
If the Devil is telling the truth,
如果那个恶魔所言属实
then we aren't able to kill it.
那我们杀不死那家伙
But I don't want to kill Denji.
但我也不打算杀死淀治
We'll starve to death if we don't do something.
可是再这样下去会饿死的
I'll use my sword if I have to.
逼不得已 我会用刀
No way.
那可不行
If he can't take care of it with a sword,
既然用刀就能解决
why not use it?
干吗不用？
He can't use the sword even if he has to.
即便逼不得已 也千万不能用刀
I feel bad for saying this but…
真到那时候 虽然很抱歉
you'll have to die if it gets that bad.
但淀治你就去死吧
It's gone.
不见了
The food on the bed…
不见了 放在床上的食物…
It's all gone.
通通没了
Why?
为什么？
Did you eat all the food?
是你这混蛋吃光的吗？
No. Denji did.
不是老子 是淀治吃掉的
How can you say that while you're still munching?
还扯那种显而易见的谎言
I see.
我知道了
I…
我…
I know now.
发现了
It's all because of this Fiend's power. That's why we can't get out.
都怪这个魔人的能力 害我们出不去八楼
It must be the case!
绝对错不了
You are wrong.
你错了
Kobeni, calm down. She's the Blood Fiend.
小红 你先冷静点
Why are you on her side?
你竟然袒护魔人
We are Devil Hunters.
我们明明是恶魔猎人
Are you with the Devil? Are you a spy?
荒井你是恶魔的伙伴吧？是间谍吧？
He's a spy.
是间谍喔
I'm not with the Devil.
我不是恶魔的伙伴
You must be a spy!
你绝对是间谍
Scream?
惨叫声？
Himeno! Run!
前辈 快跑
Kill Denji.
杀死淀治
Give me his heart.
把他的心脏给我
Give it to me.
交给我
I expand for fear.
我因恐惧而膨胀
I exist for fear.
被恐惧扼住的人
Be fearful.
更加惧怕吧
Fear death.
害怕死亡吧
Fear everything.
畏惧一切吧
Only I can kill Chainsaw.
杀死电锯的会是我
I am…
我是…
Eternity Devil.
“永远的恶魔”
It's tilting!
倾斜了
Give me Denji's heart.
把淀治的心脏交出来
Somebody!
谁都好
Kill Denji now!
你们快杀死淀治
Please kill him!
拜托快点杀了他
It's an emergency!
状况危急
Let the Devil eat him!
让恶魔吃了那家伙吧
I'm going to use the sword.
我要用刀了
Okay? Himeno…
可以吧？姬野前辈…
Himeno…
姬野前辈
Hey you!
你这家伙
What are you doing?
你在做什么
We can definitely get out if he uses that sword.
只要用那把刀 我们肯定出得去
Aki will die much sooner if he uses it.
阿秋一旦用刀 寿命将大幅缩短
He still has a lot to do.
阿秋还有许多非做不可的事
So, I'm sorry.
所以很抱歉
Denji.
淀治
I'm sorry!
抱歉
Don't touch me.
喂 别碰我
Let go of me!
给我放开
Die!
去死
I don't really care if he gets killed.
即使那家伙被刺死 那也无可奈何
That's how annoying he is.
他就是如此令人火大
But he wants to kill the Gun Devil.
但是他想杀掉枪之恶魔
To kill it,
想要杀了枪之恶魔
I need as many Devil Hunters who will fight as possible.
尽可能多一位 有骨气应战的恶魔猎人也好
Even if it means I have less time to live,
即便要缩短我的寿命
I still won't let you kill Denji.
我也不允许你们杀死淀治
Power.
帕瓦 你是血之魔人吧？
Can you stop the bleeding?
有办法帮这家伙止血吗？
I only control my own blood.
老子能操纵的只有自己的血
It's difficult to control others' blood,
虽然控制别人的血很困难…
but no one will cook for me if the samurai head is dead.
万一武士头翘辫子 就没人煮饭了
Well, guess I'll help you stop the bleeding.
没办法 我好心帮你止血吧
What do we do?
怎么办？
Aki, what should we do?
阿秋 怎么办？
It's… not my fault!
这不能怪我
It's you!
要怪你
It's all your fault!
全都是你的错
If you had let the Devil eat you,
如果你肯乖乖被恶魔吃掉
none of this would've happened.
事情就能解决了
Fine.
知道了啦
Thank goodness.
太好了
But I'll still fight back.
但我照样会抵抗
If I have a chance to kill that Devil,
假如我杀死了那个恶魔
don't forget that French kiss you promised me.
别忘了 你还要给我舌吻
Do you have a chance to win?
难道你有胜算吗？
It'll hurt like hell,
虽然痛得要命
but I'll turn into a chainsaw.
但我要变成电锯
Ch-Chainsaw…
电锯
For some reason,
不知道为什么 那个恶魔
That's why it wouldn't do it itself,
所以它不敢自己动手
but it asked you to kill me.
而是叫你们杀了我
And it kept screaming in pain while being attacked.
而且那个恶魔
So,
既然如此
why not give it hell
干脆把那个恶魔折磨到生不如死
and force it to kill itself?
逼那家伙自我了结就行了
That's a Devilish way of thinking.
这可真是恶魔的想法
Why did you have to do that for me?
你这小子干吗袒护我？
Mind your own business, you bastard.
不要多管闲事好吗？混账
I don't want to owe any more favors.
我已经受够欠别人人情了
If we get out, we'll be even.
如果我们逃得出去 就算互不相欠了